我们都还记得童年枕边的故事
We all remember the bedtime stories of our childhoods--
灰姑娘穿上水晶鞋  青蛙变王子
The shoe fits cinderella, the frog turns into a prince,
睡美人被一吻唤醒
Sleeping beauty is awakened with a kiss.
从此以后
Once upon a time..
他们过上了幸福美满的生活
And then they lived happily ever after..
童话就像美好的梦
Fairy tales, the stuff of dreams.
问题是  童话不会成真
The problem is fairy tales don't come true.
相反  那些起于阴森雨夜
It's the other stories, the ones that begin with
止于难言痛苦的故事
Dark and stormy nights and end in the unspeakable.
像噩梦一样的故事  却更加真实
It's the nightmares that always seem to become reality.
出什么事了?
What happened?
他前面一辆公车撞倒了电线杆
A bus in front of him hit a telephone pole.
他想转向  不过
He tried to swerve to miss it, but--
-有多严重?  -梅瑞狄斯
How bad is it? Meredith--
梅瑞狄斯  你要坚强点
Meredith, you're gonna have to be strong.
声明：本字幕由首发影视论坛门户站原创制作
欢迎登录首发影视论坛www.ShowFa.tv
翻译:维生素
校对: 美景 时间轴: 美景
压制: 灵溪 字幕总监: 美景
不要!
No!
那个说"从此幸福美满"的家伙
The person who invented the phrase "happily ever after"
真该被好好揍一顿
Should have his ass kicked so hard.
后退点  我喘不过气来了
Back up. You're sucking all my oxygen.
我想看清楚点
I'm trying to see.
还没出来呢  没什么好看的
It's not up yet. There's nothing to see.
-4点就该出了啊  -已经4:15了
-it's supposed to be posted at 4:00. -it's 4:15.
按刷新键  重新载入页面
Hit the refresh button. Yeah.You have to reload the page.
我每10秒刷新一次  都等等行么
I'm hitting the refresh button every ten seconds. Just wait.
-出来了吗?  -没有
-is it up yet?  -no.
-嗨  -嗨
-hi.  -hi.
-出来了吗?  -没有! 等着
-is it up yet?  -no! Wait.
我觉得我们能超过霍普金斯医院上升一名
I'm thinking we move up a slot. We pass hopkins, move up to number two.
没戏  我们还是第二
We're not passing hopkins. We're gonna stay number two.
马约诊所可能居上  我们可能排第三
Mayo could surge ahead. We could be three.
第三?
Three?
-真是悲观主义者  -是现实主义
-pessimist  -realist.
教学医院的排名跟很多方面有关
The rankings of teaching hospitals change based on any number of things.
第三也进前五了  我能接受
Ah, three is top five. I can live with three.
赶紧按刷新键吧
Just hit the refresh button.
别动  这归我管!
Get--stay back. I'm doing this.
-出来了吗?  -没有
-hey, is it up yet?  -no.
这里  按刷新键!
Well, here. Just hitthe refresh--ah-ah!
我在按刷新键呢  好  你们都退后
I am hitting the refresh.. Okay, all of you, back up.
别围着我  别瞎猜
Stop hovering, stop speculating.
排名该出来时就会出来
The rankings will go up when they go up.
他们什么时候公布  我们说了不算
We have no control over when they're posted.
出来的时候  我会说"出来咯"
When it is up, i will say, "it is up"
现在你们都退后  闭嘴  好让我按刷新...
" until then, back up, shut up and leave me alone so I can push the--
出来了
It's up.
第一名  霍普金斯医院
Oh, number one, hopkins.
-第二名  马约诊所  -我说对了吧
-number two, mayo.  -told ya.
-第三名  克里夫兰诊所  -什么?
-three, cleland clinic?  -what?
-第四名  麻省总医院  -什么?
-four, mass gen.  -what?
等等  我们掉到第五了?
Wait, wait. We moved down to five?
不是
No.
我们不是第五
We are not five.
第12名!
12!
-12名  欧麦利!  -太让人伤心了
-12, o'malley!  -it's so upsetting.
这医院不该排第十二名!
Sir--this is not a number 12 teaching hospital.
-是不该  这是座好教学医院
-no, it's a great teaching hospital.
我不要领导排名12的外科
I do not run the number 12 surgical program in the country
-头儿  -别说了 欧麦利!
-sir  -out with it, o'malley!
我们的创伤中心等级从1级掉到了2级
We've been downgraded from a level I trauma center to a level ii?
这是什么意思
What does that even mean you
你...其实不用解释
Don't need to ex-explain.
这只是细节  我走了
It's--it's just details. I can go.
第12名
12.
因为医院触了这个大霉头
You know, i couldn't ask him about
我都不敢问他何时安排我实习考试
When he was gonna schedule my intern tes
现在又是非常时期...
With all the you know what hitting the fan.
他肯定会把气出在我身上...
I mean, for all I know, he's gonna spring it to me,
有一两个小时了吧?
What, like, in an hour, two hours?
你会准备好的
And you'll be ready.
低血压的原因
Causes of hypotension.
血容量低  心肌梗塞  心律失常
Uh, hypovolemia, m.I., cardiac dysrhythmia..
-低氧血症  对吧?  -很好
-uh, hypoxia. Yeah, is that good? -very good.
真的?  什么?
Yeah?  What?
你看这雪...
The snow, it..
太漂亮了
It's--it's so pretty.
像童话里一样
It's like a fairy tale.
现在是秋天
It's--it's the fall.
这不像童话
That's not so much a fairy tale as,
这是全球变暖  是天启
Uh, it is global warming. That's the apocalypse.
这就好像  我们跌到12名
That's like--well, it's like dropping to number 12
我的实习考试也还会挂红灯
And me failing my intern test for the second time.
顺便说  我喜欢你
I adore you, by the way.
只是...
Just..
不好意思  我迟到了
Oh, hey, uh, sorry I'm late.
-我在帮...  -跟医学无关的不要谈
I was just helping--no talking unless it's medical.
我总做那个梦  德里克死了的梦
So I keep having that dream, the Derek-is-dead dream.
谁会在排名12的医院做住院医生?
You know who does their residencies at number 12 hospitals?
衰人  但我不是衰人
Losers, and I am not a loser.
去拿病历
Go get the charts.
梦里我总在担心蜡烛围成的房子
So, i mean, the dream is about me being afraid of the house of candles and,
向前跨出一大步...
You know, taking the big step and..
我居然害怕有个好结局
I'm afraid of havinga happy ending.
我有生物化学博士学位
You know, i have a phd in biochem.
我是双博士
I'm a double doctor.
双博士不该在二流医院当住院医生
Double doctors should not do their residencies at second-rate hospitals.
沃特说  我应该顺其自然  克服恐惧
Wyatt says I should just lean into the wind, into the fear,
所以我想让德里克搬来跟我住
So I'm just gonna ask Derek to move in with me.
我可以调走
I could transfer.
克里夫兰诊所在心胸方面非常不错
Cleveland clinic has a huge cardio program.
我们在前20名  还是不错的
You know, we're still in the top 20. That's pretty good.
不错是不够的
Pretty good is not enough.
我要做最好  最好的  梅瑞狄斯
I want to be great. Greatness, meredith.
"最好"  所以我想让德里克搬来住
Greatness, which is why I'm going to ask Derek to move in with me.
这是...你知道...很大的一步
It's just that it's, you know, it's a big step,
我不想再搞砸了
And I don't want to mess it up again.
我以前搞砸过
I've messed it up before--
分分合合  跟乔治上床
The breakups and the on and off again and the sleeping with George.
-这些都...  -你跟乔治上过床?
-it's just-  -you slept with George?
跟医学无关的不要谈
No talking unless it's medical.
我要这么做  让他搬来住
So I'm just gonna do it. I'm just gonna ask him to move in with me.
这么做是对的吧?
You think it's the right thing, right?
贝利呼我呢
Uh, oh, bailey's paging.
提个医学问题  梅瑞狄斯和乔治有过性行为?
Um, uh, so medically, um, meredith and George had sexual intercourse?
什么时候...几次?
Uh, when and how--how many times?
-太丢人了  -是啊
-it's humiliating.  -yeah.
12名?
12?
你是全国顶尖的脑外科医生
You're the best neurosurgeon in the country..
-谢谢  -全球顶尖
-thank you.  -in the world.
你就不能夸夸我?
Don'you want to say anything nice about me?
你是西雅图仁爱医院最好的整容医生
Uh, you're the best plastics guy at seattle grace.
不错  真会夸人
Nice, really nice.
别强迫我夸你
Don't force me to praise you.
嗨  柔思
Hey, rose.
你好  斯隆医生
Hello, dr. Sloan.
她刚开始还是接受的
She took it so well at the beginning.
希望能和睦相处  她还是我指定的手术室护士
I was hoping we could be civilized. You know, she's working my o.R.
-和睦相处不可能了  -谢谢
-civilized is out.  -thank you.
没希望了  灰飞烟灭了
It's gone. It's a trail of fairy dust.
她在"迟发性恼怒"
Now she's got delayed rage.
迟发性恼怒?
Delayed rage?
没错  之前故作坚强
Yeah, she was being big before, putting on a brave face.
现在仔细思考后  她决定对你恨之入骨
Now she's had time to think. Now she hates your guts.
你要跟她分手
You have to break up with r.
这就是了  我们已经分手了
Well, that's the point. I did already.
是你自己觉得分手了
Well, you did it personally.
你应该更"专业点"
Now you have to do it professionally.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
迟发性恼怒...
Delayed rage..
你给我列个清单...
I'd like a list..
提点改进的意见
From you of ways that I can improve.
过会再说
Not right now.
理查德  你说我不是好老师
Richard, you told me that I'm a bad teacher.
我们排12名了  我不想排12名
Now we're number 12, and I don't like to be number 12.
-所以我要个清单  -过会再说
-so I'd like alist  -not right now.
要是有什么办法能让我改进
But if there are ways that I can improve,
能让我们重回榜首
Ways that I can help the program regain its ranking,
-那么...  -外面正下着雪
-then  -it's snowing.
你知道在这华氏32度  冰天雪地的晚上
You know what happens when it's nighttime and it's snowing
会发生什么事么?
And the temperature is hovering right around 32 degrees?
不知道
No.
雪开始融化  之后又结成冰
The snow begins to melt, and then it freezes again,
结成最具杀伤力的黑冰
Creating black ice the deadliest kind
因为司机根本看不见
Of ice because it is invisible to drivers
通常这意味着  我们的急诊室会爆满
That would usually mean that our e.R.Would fill up
但现在西慈医院在外伤医院中排第一  不是我们
But mercy West is a number-i level trauma center and we're not,
病人都往他们那送
Which means their e.R.Gets the traumas
我们只捡剩的  我很生气!
While we get their castoffs, which pisses me off
所以我说"等会再说"  你就别再烦我
So when I say "not right now, " what I mean is not right now.
别抖了  丢人现眼
Stop shivering. You're embarrassing me.
没想到我们会在外面等
I didn't realize we were gonna be outside.
没事  我还好  不用了
Oh, i'm okay. You don't have to do that.
披上  你都冻紫了
Bundle up. You're turning blue.
贝利医生  外面真的很冷
Dr. Bailey, it is kind of cold out here.
-会有人来的  -没人来啊
-someone will come. -no one's coming.
也许会有老人摔坏骨盆我们就有活儿干了
Maybe some old people with broken hips we can fix.
别说了
Okay, stop talking.
不管排名前后  我们都是仁爱医院
We are seattle grace hospital, and rankings or no rankings,
我们都要站在外面  时刻准备
We are going to stand outside at the ready, on alert,
给每位到来的病人
And give the best care Available to
最好的医疗服务
Every single patient that arrives at our door
也许我们不再高居榜首
We may no longer be ranked the best,
但我是最棒的  我带你们出来的  那么你们也是最棒
But I'm the best, and you're my residents , which means you're the best.
这关乎到尊严问题  同志们
It's a matter of pride, people.
我们干什么?
What are we doing?
-等  -等什么?
-we're waiting. -for?
奇迹发生
A miracle.
会有人来的
Someone will come.
贝利医生  外伤病人都先往西慈医院送
Dr. Bailey, you know that mercy West is getting the traumas first.
会有人来的
Someone will come.
我们站在这儿  等着有人头破血流?
So we're standing out here in the hopes that someone is severely injured?
祈祷救护车会送来垂危的病人
Wishing and praying that someone is so hurt and so near death that
就因为我们比西慈更近一些?
The ambulance has to bring them here because we're closer than mercy West?
对
Yep.
你跟上帝都觉得这样挺好?
You and god are cool with that?
该死  忘了还有上帝这回事儿
Damn it. I forgot about god.
好吧  我们都进去等吧
All right. Let's just go on back inside and wait-
当心!
Hey, watch out!
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我在结冰的路上开这辆豪华轿车
I drove a limousine on ice..
全靠自己  开了10个街区
All by myself, ten blocks.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我的裙子  到处都是血  怎么回事?
My dress--there's blood all over my dress. What happened?
我只知道把大家都完整的带到医院
What happened was I got us to the hospital in one piece.
女士  请不要动  好吗?
Ma'am, pase try not to move, okay?
坐这儿别动  等轮椅过来
Just sit right here until we can get you a wheelchair.
推一个轮椅过来
We need a wheelchair over here.
病人不是我们
We're not the patient.
他叫什么来着?  本尼?  比利?
What's his name? Benny?Billy?
是这辆车的司机
The limo driver.
他从挡风玻璃飞了出去
He flew through the windshield.
请救救他
Help him, please.
杨  绕过去  帮我一把
Uh, yang, come around, help me.
拿担架  轮床  还有颈托
Get a board, uh, bring out a gurney and a c-collar.
好了  抓住
Okay, get--uh--
按住  按住
What--press it. Press.
什么情况?
What do we have?
比利 麦休  45岁  动脉破裂  未明确出血点
Billy Matthews, 45, arterial bleed, haven't isolated the cause.
我来  好  到第一外伤室
I got this. Okay, let's get him in trauma one.
-别急  我正压着出血点  -我来就行了
-okay, but I'm holding pressure over the bleed. -i got this.
我...
I just need--chie--
怎么了?
What's going on?
我去晚了  文森特该着急了
Vincent will worry if I'm late.
你们出车祸了
You've been in a car accident.
现在在医院  我们会给你最好的治疗
You're at the hospital, but we're gonna take really good care of you.
她还好吧?
Is she okay?
可能是脑震荡
Might be a concussion.
我去预约一个CT检查  排除其他问题
I'm gonna go order a c.T. And make sure it's nothing more than that.
这么多血  我们该等救护车的
All this blood--we should've waited for the ambulance.
我们等了  等了很久车都没来
We did wait. We waited, they never came.
比利就在挡风玻璃那儿挂着
And Billy was just Hanging there through the windshield.
你们把你们的司机
Wait, you guys extracted your limo
从挡风玻璃拉下来的?!
Driver from the windshield by yourselves
真勇敢
Wow, that's pretty heroic.
-迈克尔没接电话吗?  -没有  再给菲尔打
-isn't Michael answering?  -no.Try Phil again.
真不该在暴风雨中赶那该死的舞会
We shouldn't have even been going to the stupid ball in a storm like that.
什么舞会?
What ball?
冰火舞会  你相信吗?  在这样的冰暴天
The fire and ice ball--would you believe, in an ice storm?
只有语音信箱  也许他们关机了?
Just goes to voice mail. Maybe--maybe their phones are off?
你给文森特打不通?
You can't reach Vincent?
你们的丈夫在另一辆车里?
Your husbands were in another car?
我们才不和他们坐一辆车呢
We won't ride with them.
我们仨婚姻都还美满
We're three of the most happily married women
要不是老公抽雪茄
Ever except when our husbands drag out their cigars
特别是在豪华轿车里抽雪茄
And they drag out their cigars in the limo.
你的胳膊没事  只是擦伤
Well, your arm is not broken, just bruised.
欧麦利医生会帮你们缝合  没事了
So O'malley here is gonna suture up your cuts, and then you're all set.
没有其他的重伤  你们真幸运
You ladies are lucky you didn't sustain more serious injuries.
你是什么医生?  那么年轻
What kind of doctor are you? You're young.
我是实习医生
Oh, i'm an intern.
实习医生不准碰我的脸
Interns don't touch the face.
找个整形医生来
The plastic surgeon touches the face.
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
我在哪儿?
Where am i?
我们出车祸了
We were in an accident.
你没事
You're okay.
我们都会没事的
We're all gonna be fine.
-嗨  -嗨
-hi  -hi.
我最近一直挺忙
I've been really busy.
哦  我知道  我也忙得要死
No, no, i know.I've been, like, crazy busy.
查资料  做研究  泡图书馆
Researching things, a lot of research, in the library.
是啊  我也是 忙死了
Oh, yeah, me, too. Incredibly busy.
好多研究要做  和你一样  不过上网查
A lot of research, uh, like you, only I use the internet.
-我和贝利有事谈谈  -我也是
-well, i gotta check in with Bailey, so...  -me, too.
贝利  还有什么事吗?
Bailey, anything else?
没有  没什么事
Nothing. Nothing else.
问题就在这儿
That's the problem.
我在填病历  主任抢了我的病人
I'm charting. The chief took my one trauma.
我放弃了诊所  现在却只能填病历
I gave up my clinic, and now I'm charting.
主任要你看看这些
The chief wanted you to take a look at these.
比利 麦休  豪华轿车司机
Billy Matthews. He's the limo driver.
机动车事故多发伤
Multiple crush injuries from an m.V.C.
心包积血
Hemopericardium.
可以引起心脏压塞
Hemopericardium can lead to cardiac
表现为贝氏三联征
Tamponade,  which can be detected by beck's triad-
静脉压上升  动脉压下降  心包杂音
Increased j.V.P., hypotension and muffled heart sounds.
这是一家教学医院
This is a teaching hospital.
我在提高教学能力
I'm trying to improve my teaching.
别拿我当实验品
Well, don't try it on me.
-想知道我怎么教学的吗  -不
-want to know how I teach?  -no.
我就像古鲁(印度教领袖)  他们慕名而来
I'm like a guru--they  come to me for help,
我温柔地引导他们踏上真理和智慧之路
And I gently guide them along the path to truth and wisdom.
-嘿 乔治  -嗨
-hey, george.  -hi.
-我听说了件事  -什么?
-i heard a thing.  -yeah?
有点意外  无关医学
-a surprising thing, a very unexpected,
-但关于你  -等等
Nonmedical thing about you and---oh, hold on
斯隆医生  嗨
Uh, dr. Sloan, hi.
塞拉贝丝·贝利尔指定您去给她做面部缝合
Sarabeth Briar has got a facial lac, but she will only let you touch her.
你呼我就为这个?
You paged me for a cut?
你是个白痴吗  欧麦利?
What kind of moron are you, o'malley?
你是一群大白痴中最白的那个么?
Are you a special moron from the isle of complete and utter morons?
-不是的  -闭嘴
-i don't think so.  -shut up.
真理和智慧
Truth and wisdom.
他是个混球
He's an ass.
这是我们成为第12名的报应
You know what? This is what we get for being number 12--
一群穿舞裙的女人和一个半死的司机
A bunch of women in ball gowns and half-dead limo driver.
她们很不容易  她们想要救他的命
Those women are amazing. They tried to save his life.
我也想做那样的人  知道吗
That's who I want to be, you know?
做个黄脸婆?
An aging princess?
她们与自己的另一半共度一生  多幸福
They've been with the same men for years, and they're happy.
她们做得到  我也行
They did it. I can do it.
-梅瑞  我  -嘿
-mer, i  -hey.
谁呼我?
Who paged me?
是贝利和伊兹
Bailey and Izzie paged you,
你该先去找贝利  司机在她那
But you should see Bailey first because she's got the limo driver
好的
Okay.
你想搬来和我住吗?
Do you want to move in with me?
你想要同居?
You want to live together?
-我想...  如果你不愿意  -好的
-well, i an, i could--i just, uh.If--if you don't want to, i---yes.
好的?
Yes?
当然  你确定你准备好了?
Absolutely. You sure you're ready?
我正克服恐惧  拥抱一个圆满结局
I am leaning into the fear to get a happy ending.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't even know what that means.
该死!
Damn it!
死亡时间  20:47
Time of death  20:47.
豪华轿车司机  外伤致死
Limo driver, traumatic arrest.
脉搏始终未恢复
Never regained a pulse.
告诉他们  不用订手术室了
Tell them not to book the o.R.
我有一个梦想  杨
I have a dream, yang.
什么?
Excuse me?
有一天  会有外伤患者走进大门
That one day, a trauma will come through those doors--
我有一个梦想
I have a dream.
我也这么梦想
I share that dream.
12名啊
Number 12.
12名
急诊调度那有三个男人  三个重伤啊
Right now dispatch is squawking about three men--three serious injuries--
全给送到西慈医院去了
Every one, they're taking 'em to mercy West.
-三个男人?  -没错
-three men?  -that's what I said.
你说有没可能是那...
You mean like three men who could be
三个女人的丈夫?
Married to those ladies in the ball gowns
稍微有点痛
Little stick.
抓紧我的手  抓紧我的手
Squeeze my Hand. Squeeze my Hand.
就像你生皮特的时候  记得吗?
Just like when you had Pete, you remember?
生皮特没那么痛
Pete hurt less.
等发现没留下疤后  你就该好好爱我了
Yeah, but you're going to love me later when there's virtually no scar.
女士们  我刚刚和急诊调度通过电话
Ladies, um, i've been on the phone with, uh, ambulance dispatch.
三个坐豪华轿车的男士
Three gentlemen in a limousine
在马路上和另一辆车子相撞
Collided with another vehicle on broad street
可能是你们的丈夫
It's possible it was your husbands.
哦  不
Oh, no.
-救护车正送他们去西慈医院...  -在城的另一面
-they're taking them to mercy West..-which is across town.
除非你们想让他们送这儿来
Unless, uh, you prefer that they be brought here.
-我们可以这么做么?  -哦  你可以强烈要求
-we can do that? -oh, you can insist.
如果我是你  我会强烈要求的
And, uh.. If I were you, i would insist.
那么  我想  我们强烈要求
Oh, w-well, then I guess-- I guess we insist.
-是的  我们强烈要求  -你们强烈要求
-yes, we insist.  -you insist.
可以理解为  你们从西慈医院偷病人吗?
Am I to understand that you stole these traumas from mercy West?
不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
干的好  现在是私人恩怨啦
Good job, 'cause now it's personal.
杨  跟上
Yang, come with me.
-情况报告  -好的
-we have a situation.  -ok
58岁男性  机动车事故  心率160  收缩压80
58-year-old male, m.V.C., tachy and 160, b.P.80 palp,
双侧呼吸音减弱
Decreased bilateral and breath sounds.
你干了什么?
What did you do?
我什么也没干  他干的
I didn't do it. He did.
军医先生在我到之前就帮他插管了
G.I. Joe trached him at the field before I got there.
用一支笔?  你用一只钢笔给他插管?
With a pen? You trached this guy with an ink pen?
怎么了?
So?
把这人抬进去  我们走
Move this guy inside now. Come on. Let's go.
快  快  快  快
Move, move, move, move.
笔... 插管..
Pen.. Trach..
彪悍
Hot.
好了  怎么样?
Okay, what do we got?
文森特 坎纳  58岁
Vincent Kenner, 58, unrestrained backseat
轿车后座未系安全带  面部撞伤
Passenger of a limo that took a nosedive
心音低钝  头顶重创
Muffled heart sounds and large scalp lac.
-是文森特  -贝蒂
-that's Vincent.  -betty.
对不起  汉娜医生  她硬要进来
-i'm sorry, dr. Hahn, but she wanted to
文森特  他是我丈夫
See her husband. -vincent.That's my husband
出什么事了  他还好吧
What happened? Is he all right?
-我保证一有进展就通知你  -不
-i promise to give you an update as soon as we know something.  -no.
-现在  你得去做CT  -天啊
-but right now, i have to get you to the c.T.  -oh, god.
马上带你回来  马上带你回来
I'll bringou back. I'll bring you back.
腹腔积液阳性
Free fluid in the abdomen.
颅骨压缩性骨折
Compressed skullracture.
双侧呼吸音减弱
He's also got decreased breath sounds bilaterally.
这家伙要赶紧进手术室
This guy's getting an express ticket to the o.R.
告诉主任
Let the chief know.
-我能上台么  -可以
-can I scrub in?  -fine.
他喉咙里插了支钢笔
He has a pen in his throat!
哦  迈克尔!
Oh, michael!
天啊  迈克尔!  天啊  你...
Oh, god, michael!Oh, god, are you--
他喉咙里是插了一支笔吗?
Is that a--is that a pen in his throat?
还是一支圆珠笔?
Does he have a ballpoint pen in his throat?
女士  请在外面等待  让医生们工作
Ma'am, you need to wait outside. Let the doctors work.
但他们要小心啊
But they have to be very careful with him.
迈克尔最近压力很大
Michael's been under an incredible amount of stress lately and--
他最不能接受的是...
And the last thing he needs--
格蕾  你能处理好这个女人吗
Grey, can you Handle this woman, please?
卢米斯女士  我带你去见你丈夫  就在转弯处
Mrs. Loomis, we're gonna take you to your husband. He's around the corner.
宝贝  我在这儿
Sweetheart, i'm here.
迈克尔  我在这儿  宝贝
Michael, i'm here, sweetheart.
-这不是她的丈夫?  -不是
-this is not her husband?  -nope.
天啊  迈克尔!
Oh, my god, michael!
是她丈夫
It's her husband.
出什么事了?
What happened to him?
请跟我来  女士  这边走
Please come with me, ma'am. Please, this way.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
你用一支圆珠笔给他插管?
You trached a man in the field using a ballpoint pen?
我身上只带了这个
That's all I had on me.
怎么了?  我又不是没把雪弄干净
What? It's not like I didn't clean it off with fresh snow.
牛
That's awesome.
真的?  你要用6号管?
Really? You're going with a size 6 shiley tube on this?
来人把他给我拽走
Somebody get this guy away from me.
我要做个CT
Uh, i'm gonna need a c.T.
腹部CT  主任
Of, uh, this belly, chief.
克莱夫  给我们排上号
Karev, get us in line.
他的气管好像破裂了
Looks like his trachea's crushed.
我要一间手术室  再来些帮手  谁有空?
I'm gonna need an o.R. And an extra set of Hands. Who's Available?
-格蕾  -好的那个格蕾?
-grey.  -the good grey?
实习生那个
The intern Grey.
我叫欧麦利来帮忙
And I'll throw in O'malley.
哦  不错  太好了
Oh, nice. Perfect.
上帝啊  发生什么事了?
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. What happened?
轿车撞上了一堆冰
The limo hit a patch of ice.
我只记得车翻了个个  转圈  然后
Next thing I know, we're all upside down, rolling around, and now..
我腿部没知觉了
I can't feel my legs.
菲尔  我很抱歉
Oh, phil. I'm so sorry.
好  把她领出去  找谢博德会诊
Okay, get her out of here. I gotta get a consult from Shepherd.
主任  汉娜大夫有一例多发冲击伤
Oh, sir, dr. Hahn is working on multiple crash injuries.
她想让你去看看
She wants you to take a look.
好的  我这就过去
Mm-hmm, i'm on my way.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
我的车刚好在他们车后
Oh, my car was right behind theirs at the intersection.
可能是撞车时划破的
I cut it on impact.
你还对这些人进行了急救?
And you triaged these men?
欧文 亨特少校  美军外科二组
Major Owen Hunt, u.S. Army, second forward surgical.
我是创伤外科医生
I'm a trauma surgeon.
我刚休假回家
I just got home on leave.
杨大夫  处理下亨特少校的腿伤
Dr. Yang, take care of major Hunt's leg.
主任  可我要跟你一起手术
Uh, sir, i'm--i'm scrubbing in with you.
把亨特少校的腿处理好再来
After you take care of major Hunt.
你要去哪?
Hey, where are you going?
去看看我其他的病人
To check on my other patients.
不  你才是病人
No, no. You are the patient.
喂?
Hello?
你在吗?
Are you there?
我在哪?
Where am i?
你遇到交通事故  贝蒂  现在在照CT
You've been in a car accident, betty. You're having a c.T.
没事的  不要担心  尽量别动
It's gonna be okay. Everything is okay. Don't move.
有个疯子用笔给人做气管插管  真他妈酷
Some nut job down there trached a guy with a pen. Pretty freakin' cool.
想看酷的?  瞧瞧这个
You want cool? Check this out.
每30秒
Every 30 seconds.
有人吗?
Is someone there?
我在哪?
Where am i?
你遇到交通事故  贝蒂
You've been in a car accident, betty.
现在在照CT  没事的
You're having a c.T. It's okay.
每30秒她的记忆就重启  每30秒
Every 30 seconds, her memory resets--every 30 seconds.
也不坏啊
Might not be so bad.
就像"刷新"键一样  焕然一新
Like hitting the refresh button, everything is new again.
你怎么样了?
How you doing?
你问我答无数次了  我没事
You keep asking me that, and I keep telling you, i'm fine.
我知道  只是...
I know, it's just..
有时候我仍觉得丹尼就在某个角落
Sometimes I still think Denny's gonna be right around the corner,
可他已经走了很久了
And he's been dead a long time now.
有些事情是需要时间的
It just takes a while to get used to.
丽贝卡没有死  我也不会那样
Rebecca didn't die. It's not like that for me.
我很好
I'm good.
不过谢谢你的关心
But thank you for asking.
喂?
Hello?
有人吗?
Is someone there?
我在哪?
Where am i?
你在宇宙飞船里
You're in a spaceship.
要飞往月球了  旅途愉快
You're going to the moon. Enjoy the ride.
宇宙飞船?
A space ship?
什么?
Excuse me?
现在给你照CT  贝蒂
You're having a c.T., betty.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
你遇到交通事故  现在别动
You've been in a car accident. Just don't move.
多谢你了
Thanks a lot.
贝利呼我了
Bailey paged me.
回头见
I'll see you later.
凹陷性颅骨骨折
He has a depressed skull fracture.
我可以修复凹陷的颅骨
I could elevate the skull fragments,
不过目前无法估计脑损伤程度
But there's just no telling how much damage has been done.
我们必须救他
We're saving this man.
好吧  主动脉撕裂伤
All right, i think we're looking at an aortic tear,
还有大量腹腔积血
Not to mention vast amounts of blood in his abdomen
我们必须救他
We are saving this man.
腹腔出血交给我
I can Handle the abdominal bleeding.
他马上循环衰竭了
He is circling the drain.
对  我还有别的外伤病人
Yeah, i have other traumas to get to.
我们必须救他!
We are saving this man!
都听清楚了吗?  还是需要我再说一次
Now does everyone understand, or do I have to repeat myself?
-好的  主任  -知道了
-yes, sir.  -understood.
预约2号手术室
Okay, book o.R. Two.
可悲吧  不是吗
It's pathetic, isn't it--
有夫之妇跟自己最好朋友的丈夫勾搭
A married woman cheats on her best friend with her husband?
再没比这个更没品的了
You can't go much lower than that.
世事难料
These things happen.
我在商场碰到迈克尔  我们共进午餐
I ran into Michael in the mall, and we had lunch.
一星期后  我们又一起吃饭
And a week later, we had another lunch.
然后就这样了
And here we are..
8个月了  塞拉贝丝还一无所知
Eight months later, and Sarabeth has no idea.
当你决定跟某人一同生活
When you s--when you spend your life with someone and--
一起生儿育女
And you have kids together,
你以为  生活会快乐始终
You think it'll always be this amazing and this wonderful.
感情将至死不渝
You think--you think that you'll always feel that kind of love,
我也是这么认为的
And--and--and I do, i..
我是爱菲尔的
I do love Phil.
只是...
I just..
只是?
Just what?
好像自己的一部分...
Well, little pieces of you get chipped away..
被另一个人带走
By another person, and..
你想要拿回来
Then you shave little pieces of
却被带走更多
Yourself away so that you'll fit together and.
突然有一天  你抬头..
Then one day, you look up..
却发现  你已然认不出镜中的自己
And you don't even know who you are.
我最好回我丈夫身边去
I better get back to my husband.
他会开始找我的
He'll be wondering where I am.
好吧
Okay.
移植物居然真起作用了
That graft is actually holding.
我自己都很吃惊
I am impressing even myself.
嗯  就快了
Mm-hmm, almost there.
好  大家都看下显示器
All right, everybody take a look at the monitor, please.
为了拿起最后一片颅骨碎片
Now to elevate the last of the skull fragments,
我要一个大而平的器械  伸入骨下
I'll need a large, flat instrument to get under the bone.
2号拉钩
A curved number 2 penfield, please.
还是4号拉钩吧
You know what? Actually, i want my number 4 penfield.
有意思
Oh, that's interesting.
为什么你又换成4号拉钩呢
Why did you want to use the number 4 penfield instead?
什么?
I'm sorry.
我是说  你对此如何解释呢?
Oh, well, how would you explain it?
我在观摩你的教学  希望你别介意
I'm observing your teaching style. Hope you don't mind.
你换拉钩的原因是?
So the penfield--you changed it because?
我改主意了
I changed my mind.
有问题吗  柔思?
Is that a problem, rose?
当然没有  谢博德大夫
Not at all, dr. Shepherd.
你改主意了  我知道了
You changed your mind. Got it.
谢博德大夫  我有个高位脊柱伤病人
Dr. Shepherd, uh, i've got a guy with a high level spinal injury.
已经上了类固醇激素  可我觉得他需要减压
I've, uh, started him on steroids, but I believe he needs to be decompressed.
-你这边忙完了吗?  -刚好结束
-are you almost done here?  -yeah, i'm done right now.
能帮我缝合吗?
Can you close up for me?
他是个好老师  对吗?
So we consider him a good teacher, right?
我只是问问
I'm just checking.
脊柱颈6段到胸1段受创  脊髓受压
The spine's crushed from c6 to t1, impinging on the cord.
我们得开窗  减压
Yeah, we need to go in and try and relieve the pressure on the spinal cord.
-可这样的创伤..  -以后不能走路了
-but with this kind of injury-- people don't want again.
菲尔  现在还不知道结果呢
Phil, you don't know that.
安娜  甜心
Anna, sweetheart..
没事的
It's okay.
你总有办法的啊
You have to be able to do something.
菲尔很强壮  他  他都有孙子了
Phil's very strong, and he--he has grandkids.
你总得做点什么
You--you have to do something.
-你可以冷冻他  -你不能来这  我很抱歉
-you could freeze him.. -you shouldn't be in here.I'm so--
如果你还想让他下床走路的话
If you want him to have a shot at walking again.
你丫是谁?
Who the hell are you?
坏蛋军医  刚用笔给人做了气管插管
Army surgeon badass, did something crazy with a pen on a guy's throat.
请你不要给我的病人
Well, i would appreciate it if you
及其家属虚假的希望
Didn't give my patient and his wife false hope
你没试  不能说它是虚假的  这是希望
Until you've exhausted all the options, it's not false, it's just hope.
你该多关注点医学新发展
Maybe you should keep current on your research.
水牛城医院用低温确有
They did, uh, make a football player walk
让球员重新走路的报道
At buffalo gen, using therapeutic hypothermia
那个病人才20岁心血管状态良好
Buffalo gen's patient was 20 years old, in prime cardiac fitness.
而这病人60多了  这样的手术很危险
My patient is in his 60s and is a very risky candidate.
我更希望他能活着见到自己的孙子
I would prefer he live to see his grandchildren.
托瑞斯大夫  预约手术室
Dr. Torres, book an o.R.
并请告诉他
And please tell this patient that this
尽管有军医提议  还是不能手术
Procedure is not an option, despite uncle sam's assessment
现在该去缝你的腿了
We're closing up your leg now.
迈克尔能活下来吗?  他喉咙里有支笔
Michael calive after they put a pen in his throat?
能  夫人  只是为了帮他呼吸
Oh, yes, ma'am. The emergency trach helped him breathe.
斯隆医生要在手术室给他做...
Dr. Sloan needs to get him to the o.R.To sta-
手术?  他需要手术?
-surgery? He needs surgery?
你的丈夫被压在车底下
Uh, when your husband was pinned underneath the car,
气管撕裂伤  斯隆医生要修复它
He suffered a laceration to his windpipe,
斯隆医生要修复它
Which dr. Sloan needs to fix to stabilize his airway
他的肾脏和肝脏也有挫伤
He also has some bruising around his kidney and a lac on his liver.
这些也要手术吗?
Will he need surgery for th?
腹部脏器的伤有可能自愈
There's a chance the abdominal injuries will heal on their own,
但是如果继续恶化  就只能手术了
But if it ts worse, yes, will need surgery.
两个手术?
Two surgeries?
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this is happening.
-等等  这...这是今天?   -今晚午夜
-hold on. This--this is today? -tonight, midnight.
夫人  还有个小问题
Um, ma'am, there's also one other matter.
还有?  还有什么?
More? There's more?
从账单上看  你的保险今天午夜到期
Um, just according to billing, your insurance expires at midnight.
我们还是会进行治疗
So we're gonna treat you, of course,
但为了你负担轻点
But just to make it easier on you later
你还有其他的卡或者保险吗?
Is there another card or another insurance policy?
我的丈夫  都是他在料理这些事
My husband, he--he takes care of these things.
好的
Uh, okay.
好了
Okay.
我现在要麻醉  哇噢
I'm gonna numb--wow.
你还没上麻药
Uh, you're not numbed.
又怎样?
So?
怎...噢!
S--ow!
S--uh, ow.
够不到了  搭把手?
Can't get an angle on these. Could you?
好吧
Okay.
谢了
Thank you.
别客气
Don't mention it.
我能问你件事吗?
Can I ask you something?
什...什么?
Uh, w-what?
我其实要问他事情
Um, him, actually.
哦  好的  当然  我还有手术
Oh, um, yeah, sure. I've got surgery.
自己扎自己吧
And, uh, poke yourself.
跟我说说冷冻治疗的事
Talk to me about the freezing thing.
贝蒂 坎纳  轿车交通事故  颅内伤
Betty Kenner, closed head injury from the limo wreck.
硬脑膜下血肿
Subdural hematoma.
所以她会失忆
Which is why she has memory loss.
对  我们把颅压降下来就好了
Yeah. Might ease up once we relieve the pressure.
去预定一个手术室
Book an o.R.
我做完安娜丈夫的手术就做她的
I'll go in on her once I finish up on Anna's husband.
繁忙的手术日啊
Busy o.R. Today.
你不就干这个的么
But that's kinda your thing, right?
一次应付几个人
Juggling more than one person at a time.
贝蒂的丈夫怎么样了?
How's Betty's husband doing?
我正准备上台手术
Oh, i'm scrubbing in on him now.
谢博德尽力了
Shepherd did what he could,
主任和汉娜还在手术
But the chief and Hahn are still working on him
他的状况非常  非常糟糕
He is an ugly, ugly mess.
塞拉贝丝的丈夫这次手术后可能还得再动次
Sarabeth's husband may need another surgery after Derek's done with him.
可怜的女人
These poor women.
安娜...脸上有伤的那个
Well, anna--the one with the cuts--
她的丈夫是现在德里克手术的那个
Is married to the guy on Derek's table
她和塞拉贝丝老公有一腿  就是斯隆在忙的那个
And she is sleeping with Sarabeth's husband, the one Sloan's working on.
-开玩笑  -没有  别告诉贝蒂
-you're kidding.  -no.Don't tell Betty.
我告诉她了她也记不住
She wouldn't remember even if I did.
就是说  是这么回事
You mean, that's what happens?
你结婚四十年  然后变成一个大胖骗子?
You're married 40 years and then you become a big, fat lying cheater?
四十年都不足以让人负责任  还有什么能呢
I mean, if 40 years doesn't make you committed, what does?
有什么意义呢?
What's the point?
-如果我现在和德里克住到一起  -好了
-if I move in with Derek--okay, you know what?
你要能说点别的  我给你一百元
I'll give you 100 bucks if you talk about something else.
这和岁月无关  和人有关  德里克是个好男人
It's not about the years, it's about the man, and Derek is a good man.
好吧  我走了
Oh, well, i'm outta here.
有许多真正的好男人  知道吗?
There are a lot of really good men, you know?
乔治就是个真正的好男人  他...
George is a really good guy. I mean, he..
不  斯隆不是
Nope. Sloan is not.
阿历克斯  是的
Alex. Yeah.
阿历克斯已经成为一个非常好的男人
Alex has turned into a very good man.
-你和阿历克斯...  -没有
-you and Alex..  -no.
我只是说说想法
I'm making a point.
这很棒  我们是朋友  他转变了
But it is nice, you know, that we're friends, and he's changed.
他对我开诚布公
He's actually opening up to me.
如果你和他同住  结婚  四十年后
So do you think if you moved in and got married, in 40 years,
你会不会觉得心如止水  背叛他?
You'd feel dead inside enough to cheat on him?
杨  你处理好亨特少校的伤了吗?
Yang, major Hunt all taken care of?
我尽力了  头儿
Uh, i did my best, sir.
好  过来帮我压住这个出血点
Okay, come put some pressure on this bleeder for me.
你知道我怎么想吗?
You know what I think?
我认为排名12完全是个错误
I think that number 12 ranking was a mistake.
肯定是笔误
I think it was a clerical error, and I'm gonna start
我一做完手术就打电话问问
Making calls about it as soon as I get out of this surgery
我在观摩教学方式
So I've been observing teaching styles.
谢博德喜欢鼓励实习生说出想法
Shepherd likes to teach by thinking out loud.
贝利直接坦率  从不过度教导
Bailey is blunt and direct and doesn't over teach, and Sloan..
斯隆就喜欢训斥和羞辱
Well, sloan just likes to berate and humiliate.
如果你真想领会教学方法
I think if you really want to learn about teaching,
你就该和学生交流  看看怎样能学得最好
You should talk to your students, fi out how they learn best.
-没这个必要  头儿  -你是认真的么  汉娜医生?
-oh, that's not necessary, sir. -are you serious about this or not, dr. Hahn?
好吧
Fine.
说吧
Go.
对我来说  多提问我就能学好
Uh, for me, personally, i learn better when I'm asked questions.
对话教学法
The socratic method.
那是医学教育的基石
Well, that's the cornerstone of
查房的时候我们一直在这么做
Medical teaching. It's what we do in rounds
也不是每个人都能做到
Well, not everyone does it.
有的人...
Some people..
就只告诉你该干什么
Simply tell you what to do.
谁?  你是在说我吗?
Who? Are you talking about me?
他不行了  给我主动脉钳
He's crashing. Get me an aortic clamp.
我止不住肝脏出血
I can't get a Handle on this bleeding in his liver.
我们要准备善后事宜了
We may just have to start doing damage control soon.
肾动脉发现损伤
I see a tear in the renal artery.
杨  你会单层连续缝合吗?
Yang, are you familiar, with the single-layer continuous closure?
是的  主任  当然
Yes, sir. Of course.
那你来  血压还在降
All right, b.P.'s still dropping.
最大剂量肾上腺素  压住流血点
Okay, max out on levophed and keep pushing the blood.
插进去  缝合  杨
Get in there and stitch, yang.
医保出了问题
There's a problem with the insurance.
我说过  他现在不能说话
As we explained, he can't talk right now.
我知道  可是迈克尔  我打电话到医保公司
I know, but, michael, i-i called them and the credit card company,
他...他们说...
And--and they said that...
信用卡过期了
The cards have been canceled.
我... 我不理解
I... I don't understand.
我... 我想知道该怎么办
I... I just need to know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
真的很抱歉  但现在必须送他到斯隆医生那去
I'm sorry.I'm--i'm really sorry, but we need to get him to dr. Sloan now.
有什么我能做的吗?
Is there something I can do?
需要打电话给谁?
Someone I can call?
我... 我不
I... I don't.
我不管钱  可是我...
I don't Handle the money, but i...
如果你能告诉我...
If you can just tell me...
给谁打电话...
Who to call...
我跟收费处谈谈  看能帮上什么忙
I'll talk to billing and see what I can do.
谢谢你
Thank you.
卡住了
It's stuck.
左支气管那里插下不去了
I can't seem to get down the left bronchus.
就差一点了  乔治
Y-you almost got it, george.
你是干什么的  他的啦啦队?
What are you, his little cheerleader?
一边凉快去  小神童  别把事搞砸了
Step aside, wonder boy, before you make things worse.
欧麦利  去看看手术室准备好没...
O'malley, go find out if the o.R.Is ready...
这个你总能干好吧
If you can manage that.
你对乔治太苛刻了  没必要的苛刻
You're a little mean to George, un-unnecessarily mean.
他正为重考努力  已经很紧张了
And he's studying to retake his intern test, so he's a little stressed out,
我觉得或许你应该再和蔼点
So I was just thinking maybe you could be nicer.
你是实习生
You're an intern.
凭什么教训我?
Why are you talking to me?
你是我同父异母姐姐的男朋友最好的朋友 所以...
Y--well, you're my half sister's boyfriend's best friend, so i...
因为这我们就是朋友了?
You thought that makes us friends?
你以为替你的男朋友说好话  我就会听你的?
You thought that you'd defend your boyfriend to me, and I'd just take it?
他不是我男朋友
He's not my boyfriend.
但你希望他是
But you want him to be.
-我没有  -有
-i do not.  -do too.
-没有  -有
-do too.  -do too.
-他知道吗?  -闭嘴
-does he know?  -shut up.
我是主治医师  你不能叫我闭嘴
I'm your attending.You can't tell me to shut up.
你想让我对欧麦利和蔼点?
You want me to be nicer to O'malley?
求你了
Please.
向他表白  我可以考虑下
Confess your love to him, and I'll think about it.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你了解医疗保险吗?
You know anything about health insurance?
不  有什么事?
No.Why?
我想帮助一位病人
Well, i'm trying to help out a patient.
阿历克斯也不总是冷面王子啊
Oh, the softer side of Alex.
伊兹说的没错
Izzie was right.
说这话什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
-没什么  -伊兹跟你说了什么?
-nothing.  -what did Izzie say to you?
她说你是个好人
She said you were a good man.
她说你变了
She said you changed.
没什么
It was nothing.
她是不是说我哭了?
Did she say that I cried?
这是在撒谎
'cause that is a lie.
-不  她没这么说  -她不该这么多嘴
-no, she didn't say that.  -she should just keep her mouth shut.
阿历克斯  我只是说了个冷笑话
Alex, i made a stupid joke.
她只是说说而已
She didn't mean anything.
杨  怎么了?
Yang, how you doing?
我弄不好
It's, um...I can't get it.
缝不起来
It's--it's not holding.
-要裂开了 我...  -该死 杨 快点
-it's tearing.I  -damn it, yang.Move.
你说过你做过这种缝补术的
I thought you said you'd done this stitch.
我做过几百次了
I have, a hundred times.
-在心脏上  -在心脏上
-on hearts.  -hearts.
你的钳子把组织都破坏了
Your forceps were macerating the tissue.
拿结肠的手法也不对  谁教你的!
You were Handling the bowel incorrectly, which you would ow
如果你不在心胸外科花那么大精力
If you weren't allowed to clock so many hours in cardiothoracics .
根本不会丧失这些基本的外科常识
At the expense of your general surgery knowledge
糟糕  他的声带损伤已经不能修复了
Crap.His vocal cords are damaged beyond repair.
我们能做些什么?
Is there anything we can do?
他也许再也不能说话了
He probably won't talk again.
这是问我的问题
I think that question was for me.
抱歉
Sorry.
你以为可以补考
You think just 'cause you get to take your
就觉得自己很了不起么
Intern test again, that makes you big man on campus
改变不了你第一次不及格的事实
Doesn't chan the fact you failed it the first time.
-斯隆医生  -抱歉 格蕾
-dr. Sloan.  -i'm sorry, grey.
你想对这里的人说些什么吗
Was there something you wanted to say to anyone here?
不  我不想
No, there wasn't.
-胆小鬼  -闭嘴
-coward. -shut up.
血压降低
Pressure's dropping.
要室颤了
It looks like v-fib.
20焦耳
20 joules.
闪开
Clear.
再备几个单位的成份血  有多少拿多少
Give me another unit of packed cells, as many as it takes.
准备好了
Ready
拿冰冻血浆来
Somebody get me some f.F.P.
吸  快吸!
Suction, please.Suction!
失血太多了
Too much blood.
There's too much blood.
他快不行了
We're losing him.
怎么了?
What's going on?
我在医院里?
Am I in a hospital?
出了点事故  你会没事的
There was an accident, but you're going to be fine.
我们会没事的
We're all going to be fine.
我修复了您丈夫的脊椎
I was able to repair your husband's
进行了椎管减压
Vertebrae and relieve the pressure from his spine
但是
But, uh... It...
他...他还是会瘫痪?
He--he's still paralyzed?
是的  对不起
Yes, i'm sorry.
哦  天哪
Oh, god.
噢  菲尔
Oh, phil.
还有...还有迈克尔
And--and--and Michael.
迈克尔怎么样了?
What--what about Michael?
我缝合他的气管
I repaired his trachea.
不幸的是他的声带在事故中完全损伤
But unfortunately, his vocal cords were completely severed in the accident.
他哑了?
He can't talk?
他再也不能说话了?
He'll never be able to talk again?
我们得坚强点
We have to be strong.
我们得为菲尔和迈克尔坚强起来
We have to be strong for Phil and--and for Michael.
我会在第一手术室为贝蒂做准备  就等你了
I'll be ready for Betty in o.R.One when you're done here.
是关于文森特吗?
Is it Vincent?
告诉我发生了什么  求你了
Tell mewhat's happened, please.
文森特  挺过了手术
Vincent came through the surgery.
他很稳定  但是还没过危险期
He's stable but still critical.
天哪
Oh, my god.
这是杨医生
This is dr. Yang.
她今晚全权负责
She is going to be personally responsible for
照管您丈夫
Seeing to it that your husband makes it through the night
我...
I'm...
我会及时通知您情况的
I will keep you posted.
及时通知我... 通知什么?
Keep me posted... About what?
我在哪里?
Where am i?
文森特在哪里?
Where's Vincent?
她得了硬脑膜下血肿
She has a subdural hematoma.
每30秒钟记忆就会重启一次
Her memory resets every 30 seconds.
真好啊
Perfect.
给你的  谢谢
That's for you.Thank you.
求求你看看我
Please look at me.
如果你总这样  你就别在我的手术室干了
If you're gonna behave like this, you can't be in my o.R.
好的  这很不好开口
Okay, there's no good way to say this.
我这个样子是  因为我...
I'veeen acting this way because I'm...
我怀了你的孩子  德里克
I'm carrying your child, derek.
哈  骗到你了
Gotcha.
你怎么开这种玩笑?
This is your idea of a joke?
哦  得了吧
Oh, please.
你活该
You deserve it.
你以为你是谁啊?
Who do you think you are?
如果你老这样  别在我的手术室干了
If you're gonna keep behaving this way, you can't be in my o.R.
你可以调往别的科室
You should transfer to a different specialty.
You should transr to a different specialty.
我是个神经外科医生
I'm a neurosurgeon.
你当时总强调不喜欢前女友时
You shoulda thought of that while
你就应该想到这点了
Repeatedly assuring me that you were over your ex
手术室见
I'll see you in the o.R.
我就在那等你
I'm not going anywhere.
头儿  谢博德的脊柱病人  菲利普 卢米斯
Chief, about Phillip Loomis, shepherd's spinal patient?
我在考虑
Um, i was thinking...
低温治疗怎么样?
What about therapeutic hypothermia?
你想冰冻脊柱损伤?
You want to freeze a spinal injury?
水牛城和麻省有过先例
They did it in buffalo, and mass gen had
亨特少校极力推荐
Success with it, too, and major Hunt--he swears by it
谢博德自己怎么想
What does Shepherd think?
他觉得卢米斯先生有点冒险  他年纪比较大
He thinks it's too risky in mr.Loomis' case, that he's not as fit, is older.
卢米斯不会比我大吧
Loomis isn't much older than me.
我可以来做  头儿
I can do the procedure, chief.
只是需要你的允许
I just need your okay.
你刚才在后面干嘛呢
What were you doing back there?
我在帮你
I was trying to help you.
在主治手术时让他闭嘴  这可不是在帮我
Telling an attending to shut up in his o.R--that's not helping.
你怎么知道你这么做没事呢
What makes you think you can get away...
你跟他上床了?
You're sleeping with him?
-什么?  没有  -不  你有
-what?No.  -yes, you are.
-你  -你干嘛那么说
-you  -why would you even say that?
等等  你吃错?
Wait, are you jealous?
我吃错你就能让斯隆闭嘴?
Of the fact that you can tell Sloan to shut up?
好吧
Yeah.
但你知道  他说的对
But, you know, he's right.
我就是这家医院的笑话  都是我的错
I'm the hospital joke, and it's my fault.
就我自己没过实习考试
I'm the one who failed my intern exam and
赌城结婚  然后背叛妻子
Got married in vegas and cheated on my wife
不  你没明白
No.You don't understand.
-他说你的唯一原因是  -无所谓了
-the only reason that he was picking on you is--no, it doesn't matter.
我自己能搞定
I can take care of myself.
他有钓鱼的装备  靴子  还有护发品
So--and he's got fishing gear and boots and hair products.
我可没那么大地方装这些东西
I don't have room for any of that stuff.
而且他很爱说话  滔滔不绝
And he talks, and not a little.
我是说  他爱说话  没完没了的说
I mean, he chats he's chatty freakin' cathy..
等会再说吧
Not right now.
你知道他搬进来之后会怎样  对吧
And then you know what's gonna happen after he moves in, don't you?
我们在他的地上建房子
We build a house on his land,
结婚  成为共有财产
Which will be our land because we'll be married
然后我就是谢博德医生夫人
And then I'll be dr. Mrs.Shepherd.
然后你也能想到吧
And you know what comes after that, don't you?
孩子  他的孩子们
Babies, and they'll be hisabies,
头发漂亮  能说会道
So they'll have perfect hair and they'll be chatty
五个爱说话的小孩外加老公
So I'll have five chatty children,
住在郊外房子里
A chatty husband and live in a house in the wilderness
然后我就会开始想跟你老公上床
And then I'll start sleeping with your husband.
我要告诉他我改主意了
I gotta tell him I changed my mind.
-你不觉得吗  -梅瑞狄斯
-don't you think?  -meredith!
怎么了
What?
-你干嘛摆张臭脸?  -别说了
-why are you making that face?  -shut up.
别再提德里克
You know, just shut up about Derek.
别再提跟德里克住在一起
Shut up about moving in with Derek.
别再提你们的关系  知道为什么吗
Shut up about your relationship because you want to know why?
我早就听过八百六十遍了
I've heard it all before.
你俩在一起  我得听你说一遍
Yeah, you know, you guys get together, and I have to listen to it,
你俩分手  我还要听一遍
And then you guys break up, and I have to listen to it.
我今天手术差点害死一个人
I almost killed a man in surgery today.
我
I...
你想知道我的想法?
Okay, you want--you want to know what I think?
你真的想知道?
Okay, you--you really want to know?
你和德里克没戏
You and Derek will not work.
搬到一起就是最大的错误
Moving in together is a mistake of massive proportions.
梦见死去的德里克  这就说明你俩没戏
You are dreaming of dead Derek, which should tell you it will not work!
-克里斯蒂娜 我  -别别 你知道
-cristina, i  -no no you know
什么永远幸福美满  根本不存在
This whole thing, this happily ever after does not exist.
拜托你  当你考虑作出选择时
So please, please, please, as you weigh your options here, just, you know,
请闭嘴  安静的考虑
Consider the possibility of shutting the
因为我不想再听了
Hell up, because I can't listen to it anymore
-我  -别说了
-i  -no.
-好吧  -别
-okay  -no!
-好吧  -就这样 我说完了
-i--okay, that'sit.I'm done.
我不会说你活该  但你确实活该
I'm not gonna say you deserved that, but you deserved that.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
帮我  扶我起来
Oh, help me... Help me up.
别动
Don't move.
我去找人
I'm gonna go get some help.